Guide to the American Society of Planning Officials Records, 1925-1982
American Society of Planning Officials Records, 1925-1982
- Series VIII. ASPO files regarding Association of State Planning and Development Agencies
  - Special - ASPDA folder for ASPO, 1947-1953 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Special - ASPDA folder for ASPO, 1951-1952 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Special - ASPDA folder for ASPO, 1951-1953 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - ASPDA - financial transfer, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - ASPDA - post-affiliation with ASPO, 1953-1955 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - ASPDA - post-affiliation with ASPO, 1956-1957 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Series IX. ASPO files regarding International Federation for Housing and Town Planning (later International Federation for Housing and Planning)
  - XVIth International Housing and Town Planning Congress, 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - International Federation for Housing and Town Planning (IFHTP_, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - IFHTP, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 3-5)
  - IFHTP, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 6-8)
  - IFHTP, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 9-10)
  - IFHTP, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 11-12)
  - IFHTP, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
  - IFHTP, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 15-16)
  - IFHTP, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 17-19)
  - IFHTP correspondence - Charles Ascher, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 20-21)
  - IFHTP correspondence - Van der Weijde, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - IFHTP, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 23-26)
  - IFHTP correspondence - Van der Weijde, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 27-28)
  - IFHTP United States Committee general correspondence, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 29-32)
  - IFHTP, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 33-34)
  - IFHTP United States Committee minutes, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - IFHTP United States Committee membership campaign, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 36-37)
  - IFHTP, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 39-40)
  - IFHTP correspondence - Charles Aschler, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - IFHTP correspondence - Van der Weijde, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - IFHTP Congress, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
  - IFHTP, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - IFHTP correspondence - Van der Weijde, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - IFHTP, 1955-1961 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - International Federation for Housing and Planning (IFHP), 1958-1962 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - IFHP, 1960-1965 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - IFHP, 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - IFHP, 1965-66 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - IFHP organization, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - IFHP Bureau, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - IFHP Bureau, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - IFHP Bureau, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - IFHP Bureau, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - IFHP Bureau, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - IFHP Bureau, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - IFHP correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - IFHP correspondence, 1961-1977 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - IFHP correspondence - L.P. Gelpke, 1960-1965 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - IFHP correspondence - L.P. Gelpke, 1966-1969 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - IFHP correspondence - Jon H. Leons, 1970-1973 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - IFHP correspondence - Jon H. Leons, 1974-1980 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - IFHP correspondence - Vagn Rud Nielson, 1971-1977 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - IFHP program and policy, 1952-1971 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - IFHP program and policy, 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - IFHP Officers Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - general, 1962-1972 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Environment; IFHP Standing Committee - Developing Countries (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Historic Urban, 1963-1971 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Professional Planners, 1961-1967 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Rent and Family Income, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Social Housing (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Traffic Problems, 1959-71 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Urban Renewal, 1958-1962 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Urban Renewal, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Urban Renewal, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Urban Renewal, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - IFHP Standing Committee - Urban Renewal, 1965-1967 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - IFHP - HUD materials, 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - IFHP - ASPO-AIP-NAHRO joint activities, 1961-1973 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - IFHP - East Asia Regional Organization for Planning and Housing, 1964-1972 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - IFHP New Sheet, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - IFHP Exhibits, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - IFHP Finances, 1952-1974 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - IFHP Finances, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - IFHP Finances; ASPO contributions, 1962-1971 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - IFHP - secretaries/directors of national organizations, 1964-1967 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - IFHP - selection of new secretary-general, 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - IFHP - United Nations, 1964-1971 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - IFHP - United States Federal Participation, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - IFHP - United States members, 1962-1972 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - IFHP - United States solicitations, 1957-1968 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - IFHP - seminar on urban renewal, 1958-1960 (Box 41, Folder 10-12)
  - IFHP - World Town Planning Day, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - IFHP - Metropolitan Association of Urban Designers and Environmental Planners (MAUDEP), 1975 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - North American Urban Liaison Office (NAULO), 1979 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - IFHP Congress - Liege, Belgium, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 16-17)
  - IFHP Congress - Perugia, Italy, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - IFHP Congress - San Juan, 1959-60 (Box 41, Folder 19-20)
  - IFHP Congress - San Juan - Soviet Exchange, 1955-1962 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - North American Regional Section (NARS) of IFHP, 1977-1979 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - NARS-IFHP - agendas/minutes, 1974-1979 (Box 41, Folder 23-24)
  - NARS-IFHP - member organizations correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - NARS-IFHP - U.N. liaison, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - NARS-IFHP - mailing list, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - NARS-IFHP - IFHP correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - NARS Border Cities Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - NARS-IFHP - projects - Habitat Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - NARS-IFHP - projects - Habitat Position Paper, 1974-1976 (Box 41, Folder 31-32)
  - NARS-IFHP - projects - visitors guide, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - NARS-IFHP - secretariat services (ASPO), 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 34-36)
  - NARS-IFHP - United States committees (lists of people with international interests) (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - IFHP - Rafsky, 1975-1979 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - IFHP - organization rules, etc., 1958-1967 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - IFHP Bureau, 1959-1977 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - IFHP Council, 1938, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - IFHP Council, 1971-1979 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Series X. Audiotapes of Hugh Pomeroy (former Executive Director)
  - Conference with Hugh Pomeroy taped in his offices in White Plains, N.Y., June 15, 1961 (interviewer is not identified; in 1961 Pomeroy was the Director of the Westchester Co., N.Y. Dept. of of Planning), tr620
  - Pomeroy's address at a park, recreation, and open space conference in Bucks Co., Pa., 1959, tr620
- Series IX. Photographs
  - History of Activities - Photos (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Convention Dinner, May 16, 1939; Mapcase